<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>web on Javier Lopez</title>
    <link>https://javier-lopez.me/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web on Javier Lopez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://javier-lopez.me/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using Puppeteer to read table data</title>
      <link>https://javier-lopez.me/blog/puppeteer_read_table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://javier-lopez.me/blog/puppeteer_read_table/</guid>
      <description>What is Puppeteer? Puppeteer is a Node library which provides a high-level API to control Chrome or Chromium over the DevTools Protocol. Puppeteer runs headless by default, but can be configured to run full (non-headless) Chrome or Chromium.
Why use Puppeteer? Imaging that there is not an API to get data from a public site. Using Puppeteer you are able to render the content a web page and scrap data from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Force Integration</title>
      <link>https://javier-lopez.me/achievements/salesforce_integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://javier-lopez.me/achievements/salesforce_integration/</guid>
      <description>The Problem Upload the list of phone numbers to dial that were in Salesforce to Connect First. Send and keep the products and prices entered in Salesforce updated in the dialer.
The Solution Develop a website that is responsible for retrieving information from Salesforce and uploading it to the customer&amp;rsquo;s database. After this, the information is sent to the Connect First dialer to be used.
Technology Used  ASP .NET C# REST API MSSQL Angular2+ HTML/CSS SASS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect First Integration</title>
      <link>https://javier-lopez.me/achievements/connect_first_integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://javier-lopez.me/achievements/connect_first_integration/</guid>
      <description>The Problem The need to automate the generation of reports and keep the information updated from our database to the dialer.
The Solution I was the developer in charge of building a workflow so that the dialer administrators could manage the dialer information with the client&amp;rsquo;s database. For example, when a new agent is created on the customer&amp;rsquo;s system, access to the dialer will also be created.
To keep the information in our reports always updated, I created services so that the dialer could make requests to us with the information of the call and in this way be able to save it in the customer&amp;rsquo;s database.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
